<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>💜 Welcome to SpeechEvalPro! on</title><link>https://kevinkaul.github.io/</link><description>Recent content in 💜 Welcome to SpeechEvalPro! on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://kevinkaul.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Public Parameters</title><link>https://kevinkaul.github.io/mode/common/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kevinkaul.github.io/mode/common/</guid><description>1. Evaluation parameters # StartMessage # field type remark defaults langType enum english：en-US
chinese：zh-cmn-Hans-CN required connectTimeout int Connection 、Heartbeat timeout (seconds), range: 5-60. 15 responseTimeout int Response timeout (seconds), range: 5-60. 15 rank int Scoring scale, range: 1-100 100 precision float Score ad:justment coefficient, range: 0.8-1.5 (up to 3 decimal places)The function of this coefficient is to adjust up or down the score between 30 and 90 (percentage system), and the scores in other ranges remain unchangedWhen precision &amp;gt;1.</description></item><item><title>Question type introduction</title><link>https://kevinkaul.github.io/mode/intro/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kevinkaul.github.io/mode/intro/</guid><description>English question type # langType：en-US
name mode Audio duration limit Reference text length limit phoneme phoneme 20 s 100 characters word word 20 s 100 characters sentence sentence 40 s 300 characters paragraphs chapter 300 s 10000 characters Chinese question type # langType：zh-cmn-Hans-CN
name mode Audio duration limit Reference text length limit phoneme phoneme 20 s 100 characters word word 20 s 50 characters sentence sentence 40 s 100 characters paragraphs chapter 300 s 1000 characters</description></item><item><title>Quick Start</title><link>https://kevinkaul.github.io/setup/quick_start/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kevinkaul.github.io/setup/quick_start/</guid><description>1. Get the appKey and appSecret # You need to contact us to obtain an API key. Please contact us by
visiting SpeechEvalPro website
clicking Start free trial / Buy now button and fill in a form.
We&amp;rsquo;ll get in touch with you in 1 business day.
2. Git clone the samples to your local # git clone https://github.com/KevinKaul/speechevalpro-api-samples.git 3. Identify your needs # question type (mode) : phoneme、word、sentence、chapter</description></item><item><title>English special label format</title><link>https://kevinkaul.github.io/datadict/annotation-en/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kevinkaul.github.io/datadict/annotation-en/</guid><description>In different English question types, the reference text (refText) supports the input of multiple annotation formats to meet the requirements of specific reading methods.
When passing in parameters, use the corresponding annotation format directly in the refText field, for example:
{ &amp;#34;mode&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;sentence&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;refText&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;It&amp;#39;s mine, isn&amp;#39;t it(t:1)?&amp;#34; } Question type is supported, which means that parameters are passed in according to the specified format, and scoring will be performed according to this format.</description></item><item><title>Hanyu Pinyin Scoring</title><link>https://kevinkaul.github.io/mode/zh-basic/phoneme/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kevinkaul.github.io/mode/zh-basic/phoneme/</guid><description>wss://api.xxxxx.com/zh-cmn-Hans-CN/phoneme
Limit # send audio up to 20 seconds long reference text up to 100 characters. Parameter # field type defaults remark mode string required phoneme refText string required Reference text, supporting consonants, rhymes, unvoiced syllables, voiced syllables, no more than 100 charactersOnly supports pinyin representation in SpeechEvalPro format —— Chinese special label format . Multiple consonants, rhymes, and syllables are separated by English spaces.</description></item><item><title>Phoneme Scoring</title><link>https://kevinkaul.github.io/mode/en-basic/phoneme/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kevinkaul.github.io/mode/en-basic/phoneme/</guid><description>wss://api.xxxxx.com/en-US/chapter
Limit # send audio up to 20 seconds long reference text up to 100 characters. Parameter # field type defaults remark mode string required phoneme refText string required reference text Only phoneme representation in SpeechEvalPro format is supported, see English Phonetic Symbol Comparison Table for details. Multiple phonetic symbols are separated by English spaces [!</description></item><item><title>Warnings</title><link>https://kevinkaul.github.io/datadict/ecode/warnings/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kevinkaul.github.io/datadict/ecode/warnings/</guid><description> Type Code Message Tips Developers Remark Audio 35003 audio length is 0 Check the audio data length If the audio duration is 0, the warning callback returns the evaluation result Audio 35102 audio length exceeded Control the user&amp;rsquo;s recording time on the interactive interface to avoid excessive recording For details, please refer to the Introduction to Questions document Audio 35001 audio data is too short Control the user&amp;rsquo;s recording time on the interactive interface to avoid recording too short 0&amp;lt;Audio duration&amp;lt;240ms Audio 35002 audio volume is too low Check the recording for correctness The volume is too low （When the audio is short and the volume is low, the priority is to return The volume is too low）</description></item><item><title>- 1. Generate JWT token</title><link>https://kevinkaul.github.io/setup/usage/token/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kevinkaul.github.io/setup/usage/token/</guid><description>Assume that you already have AppKey and AppSecret, and know the domain name address to request.
Get Token By API # curl -X POST &amp;#39;https://{{$HOST}}/auth/generateToken&amp;#39; \ --header &amp;#39;Content-Type: application/json&amp;#39; \ --data &amp;#39;{ &amp;#34;timestamp&amp;#34;:{{$timestamp}}, &amp;#34;signature&amp;#34;:{{$signature}}, &amp;#34;appKey&amp;#34;:&amp;#34;{{$appKey}}&amp;#34; }&amp;#39; e.g.
{ &amp;#34;timestamp&amp;#34;:1690637789, &amp;#34;signature&amp;#34;:&amp;#34;FEecGK0xbTOF3yxH3zq11FgkqFg=&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;appKey&amp;#34;:&amp;#34;01e93ab5-dcb2-4c6b-a321-02c0c8d3831&amp;#34; } // appSecret : 04a013293939f96 How the signature is constructed # Step 1: Construct a normalized request string stringToSign using the appKey and timestamp request parameters (note the order of the parameters), such as:</description></item><item><title>Chinese special label format</title><link>https://kevinkaul.github.io/datadict/annotation-zh/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kevinkaul.github.io/datadict/annotation-zh/</guid><description>In different Chinese question types, the reference text (refText) supports the input of multiple annotation formats to meet the requirements of specific reading methods.
When passing in parameters, use the corresponding annotation format directly in the refText field, for example:
{ &amp;#34;mode&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;word&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;refText&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;长(zhang3)长(chang2)&amp;#34; } Pass in the parameters according to the specified label format, and the score will be scored according to this format
Notice</description></item><item><title>Errors</title><link>https://kevinkaul.github.io/datadict/ecode/errors/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kevinkaul.github.io/datadict/ecode/errors/</guid><description> Type Code Message Tips Developers Remark Authorization 34006 app no available times Contact us to increase the number of calls The remaining number of callables is 0 Authorization 34005 concurrency error Control concurrency or contact us to increase the concurrency quota The AppKey concurrency limit is exceeded Authorization 34013 this language capability has expired AppKey is expired. Contact us to renew The appKey usage period has been exceeded Authorization 34003 internal service error Try again, if you still can&amp;rsquo;t solve it, you need to contact us to confirm the status of the online service Authorization 34002 JSON serialization failed Check the JSON format The send JSON is malformed Authorization 34056 token has expired, please get it again Regenerate the token When a WebSocket connection is established, the token expires Authorization 34015 token format error, please get it again Regenerate the token When establishing a WebSocket connection, token error Authorization 34011 signature error Check the appSecret and the algorithm method of generating signatures, if you still can&amp;rsquo;t solve it, you need to contact us String concatenation error or appSecret error Authorization 34012 appKey is not available Contact us to confirm the appKey status The appKey feature is disabled Authorization 34033 appKey does not exist Check the appKey The appKey fdoes not exist Authorization 32157 failed to generate token Try again, if you still can&amp;rsquo;t solve it, you need to contact us to confirm the status of the online service Server-side error Authorization 34025 invalid current timestamp Correct the system time The device time differs from the system time by more than 1 hour Authorization 34026 concurrency exceeded Try again, if you still can&amp;rsquo;t solve it, you need to contact us to confirm the status of the online service Decoder concurrency limit exceeded Authorization 34023 unsupported language capability Contact us to confirm the authorization The appKey does not support that language Connection 37111 wrong order of calls Call in the correct order Establish ws connection =&amp;gt;startMsg =&amp;gt; sendAudioData =&amp;gt;stopMsg Connection 37112 read client data timeout Try again If the client data is not received for a long time, the WebSocket connection is disconnected, and a weak network environment may occur Parameter 37123 parameter type error The request parameter type is incorrect For details, please refer to the Introduction to Questions document Parameter 37124 parameter missing Check the langType/refText/mode parameters Required parameters are missing Parameter 37125 parameter error The request parameter value is incorrect Parameter 37126 refText is empty Check the content of the reference text (1) The input text is empty&amp;lt; br /&amp;gt; (2) The input text contains only punctuation marks, non-evaluation language characters, similar (t:1) and other prosody labels Parameter 37127 refText is exceeded Check the reference text length Reference text length exceeded Internal scoring 383xx evaluation failed Contact us to confirm the specific error condition Make a note of the evalId Internal scoring 33112 get result timeout Service processing timed out Audio 33100 audio format does not match req parameter Check the audio format and format parameters Check the audio format and format parameters to make sure they are consistent</description></item><item><title>Word Scoring</title><link>https://kevinkaul.github.io/mode/en-basic/word/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kevinkaul.github.io/mode/en-basic/word/</guid><description>wss://api.xxxxx.com/en-US/word
Limit # send audio up to 20 seconds long reference text up to 100 characters. Parameter # field type defaults remark mode string required word refText string required reference text Reference text support English special label format [!EXAMPLE] Examples
{ &amp;#34;mode&amp;#34;:&amp;#34;word&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;refText&amp;#34;:&amp;#34;hello world&amp;#34; } Evaluation Results # A complete example of the JSON response result field type remark evalId string evalId timestamp integer task timestamp attachAudioUrl string audio storage url (this field is only returned when the question type parameter attachAudioUrl=true) audioInfo dict Audio Quality Information refText string reference text hypothesis string actual text read overall double total score (range determined by scale) accuracy double accuracy (range determined by point scale) waveTime integer actual recording time（ms） startTime integer the starting reading position in a recording (ms)（ms） endTime integer the ending reading position in a recording (ms)（ms） wordInfo list&amp;lt;dict&amp;gt; array of word info objects (👇) wordInfo # field type remark refText string reference text hypothesis string actual text read score double total score (range determined by scale) accuracy double word accuracy (range determined by point scale) rhythm dict **word rhythm info objects ** ├─ stressRef integer word stress label (1 means it should be accented, 0 means it shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be accented/do not check) ├─ stressScore integer word stress score (1 means actually agrees with label, 0 means doesn&amp;rsquo;t match/do not check) type string word type startTime integer the starting reading position in a recording (ms) endTime integer the ending reading position in a recording (ms) syllables list&amp;lt;dict&amp;gt; array of syllable info objects, refer to SpeechEvalPro scheme English Phonetic Symbol Comparison Table ├─ syllable string phonemic composition of syllables.</description></item><item><title>Word Scoring</title><link>https://kevinkaul.github.io/mode/zh-basic/word/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kevinkaul.github.io/mode/zh-basic/word/</guid><description> wss://api.xxxxx.com/zh-cmn-Hans-CN/word
Limit # send audio up to 20 seconds long reference text up to 50 characters. Parameter # field type defaults remark mode string required word refText string required reference text Reference text support Chinese special label format [!EXAMPLE] Examples
{ &amp;#34;mode&amp;#34;:&amp;#34;word&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;refText&amp;#34;:&amp;#34;明天 明儿&amp;#34; } Evaluation Results # A complete example of the JSON response result field type remark evalId string evalId timestamp integer task timestamp attachAudioUrl string audio storage url (this field is only returned when the question type parameter attachAudioUrl=true) audioInfo dict Audio Quality Information refText string reference text pinyin string pinyin transcription of the corresponding reference text (with tones) overall double total score (range determined by a point system)combines the toneless pronunciation of syllables (phn) and tones (toneScore) phn double pronunciation accuracy without tones (range determined by a point system) toneScore double overall tone score (range determined by point system) waveTime integer actual recording duration (ms) startTime integer the starting reading position in a recording (ms) endTime integer the ending reading position in a recording (ms) characters list&amp;lt;dict&amp;gt; array of characters info objects (👇) characters # field type remark refText string reference text pinyin string pinyin transcription of the corresponding reference text (without tones) overall double total score (range determined by a point system)combines the toneless pronunciation of syllables (phn) and tones (toneScore) phn double pronunciation accuracy without tones (range determined by a point system) toneRef integer standard tones (0 to 4 for soft, one to four tones respectively) toneConfidence list&amp;lt;integer&amp;gt; tone confidence level (range 0 to 100, elements in order: soft, one to four) toneScore double overall tone score (range determined by point system) erRef int codified sound labels (1 means it should be pronounced, 0 means it should not be pronounced/not checked) erScore int score for paedophones (1 indicates actual agreement with label, 0 indicates actual inconsistency with label/no check) type string word type startTime integer the starting reading position in a recording (ms) endTime integer the ending reading position in a recording (ms) phonemes list&amp;lt;dict&amp;gt; array of phonemes info objects ├─ phoneme string transcription representation of sounds and rhymes ├─ score double vocalization score (range determined by point system) ├─ startTime integer the starting reading position in a recording (ms) ├─ endTime integer the ending reading position in a recording (ms)</description></item><item><title>- 2. Websocket streaming evaluation</title><link>https://kevinkaul.github.io/setup/usage/ws/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kevinkaul.github.io/setup/usage/ws/</guid><description>Evaluation flowchart # mermaid.initialize({ "flowchart": { "useMaxWidth":true }, "theme": "default" } ) sequenceDiagram Client-Server: Establish a connection (Carry the token in the header or in the url) Server--Client: The connection was successful Client-Server: StartMessage Server--Client: StartedMessage loop Client-Server: Send audio data (binary) Server-Client: Returns real-time results (if you send startMsg with real-time and sentence or paragraph type) end Client-Server: StopMessage Server--Client: (Result &amp;&amp; CompletedMessage) || (ErrorMessage &amp;&amp; CompletedMessage) Request Host URL # wss://{{ApiHost}}/{{LangType}}/{{QuestionType}}</description></item><item><title>Other parameters</title><link>https://kevinkaul.github.io/datadict/other/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kevinkaul.github.io/datadict/other/</guid><description>Character/phrase/phoneme type # The type field in the returned result of the evaluation indicates the word (word/phoneme) type, and the values are as follows:
normal：normal insert：read more repeat：repeated read delete：missed reading replace：misspelled oov：Indicates that the word (phrase) is not in the system library, and the word (phrase) cannot be scored</description></item><item><title>Sentence Scoring</title><link>https://kevinkaul.github.io/mode/en-basic/sentence/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kevinkaul.github.io/mode/en-basic/sentence/</guid><description>wss://api.xxxxx.com/en-US/sentence
Limit # send audio up to 40 seconds long reference text up to 300 characters. can be set to enable real-time return results Evaluation parameters Parameter # field type defaults remark mode string required sentence refText string required reference text Reference text support English special label format [!EXAMPLE] Examples
{ &amp;#34;mode&amp;#34;:&amp;#34;sentence&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;refText&amp;#34;:&amp;#34;Hello world.</description></item><item><title>Sentence Scoring</title><link>https://kevinkaul.github.io/mode/zh-basic/sentence/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kevinkaul.github.io/mode/zh-basic/sentence/</guid><description>wss://api.xxxxx.com/zh-cmn-Hans-CN/sentence
Limit # send audio up to 40 seconds long reference text up to 100 characters. can be set to enable real-time return results Evaluation parameters Parameter # field type defaults remark mode string required sentence refText string required reference text Reference text support Chinese special label format phonemes boolean false whether or not to return sound and rhyme information [!</description></item><item><title>English Phonetic Symbol Comparison Table</title><link>https://kevinkaul.github.io/datadict/phoneme/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kevinkaul.github.io/datadict/phoneme/</guid><description>[!tip] Hint
This document is used for the comparison and conversion of English phonetic symbols
Vowel # Single Sound # ID SpeechEvalPro Scheme CMUBET KK DJ(2015)
IPA(88) word example SpeechEvalPro Scheme Transcription Result 1 iy iy /i/ /i:/ eat iy t 2 ih ih /ɪ/ /ɪ/ it ih t 3 eh eh /ɛ/ /e/ bed b eh d 4 ae ae /æ/ /æ/ at ae t 5 aa aa /ɑ/ /ɑ:/ car k aa r 6 ao ao /ɔ/ /ɔ:/ tall t ao l 7 oo - - /ɒ/ ox oo k s 8 uw uw /u/ /u:/ too t uw 9 uh uh /ʊ/ /ʊ/ put p uh t 10 ah ah /ʌ/ /ʌ/ hut hh ah t 11 ax - /ə/ /ə/ of ax v Diphthongs # ID SpeechEvalPro Scheme CMUBET KK DJ(2015)</description></item><item><title>Paragraphs Scoring</title><link>https://kevinkaul.github.io/mode/en-basic/chapter/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kevinkaul.github.io/mode/en-basic/chapter/</guid><description>wss://api.xxxxx.com/en-US/chapter
Limit # send audio up to 300 seconds long reference text up to 10,000 characters. can be set to enable real-time return results Evaluation parameters Parameter # field type defaults remark mode string required chapter refText string required reference text Reference text support English special label format [!EXAMPLE] Examples
{ &amp;#34;mode&amp;#34;:&amp;#34;chapter&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;refText&amp;#34;:&amp;#34;Don’t forget to carry the token obtained in the first step in the header.</description></item><item><title>Paragraphs Scoring</title><link>https://kevinkaul.github.io/mode/zh-basic/chapter/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kevinkaul.github.io/mode/zh-basic/chapter/</guid><description>wss://api.xxxxx.com/zh-cmn-Hans-CN/chapter
Limit # send audio up to 300 seconds long reference text up to 2000 characters. can be set to enable real-time return results Evaluation parameters Parameter # field type defaults remark mode string required chapter refText string required reference text Reference text support Chinese special label format phonemes boolean false whether or not to return consonant vowel information [!</description></item><item><title>Chinese Pinyin Comparison Table</title><link>https://kevinkaul.github.io/datadict/pinyin/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kevinkaul.github.io/datadict/pinyin/</guid><description> [!tip] Hint
This document is used for Chinese Pinyin format comparison and conversion
consonant, soundproof letter # b p m f d t n l g k h j q x zh ch sh r z c s y w vowels # ID SpeechEvalPro Scheme Chinese Pinyin Scheme Chinese Character Example SpeechEvalPro Scheme Transcription Result 1 a a 阿 a1 2 o o 波 bo1 3 e e 特 te4 4 i i 以 yi3 5 u u 布 bu4 6 v ü 绿 lv4 7 ai ai 太 tai4 8 ao ao 包 bao1 9 an an 看 kan4 10 ang ang 上 shang4 11 ou ou 口 kou3 12 ong ong 空 kong1 13 ei ei 美 mei3 14 er er 儿 er2 15 en en 本 ben3 16 eng eng 冷 leng3 17 iu iu 牛 niu2 18 ie ie 列 lie4 19 in in 宾 bin1 20 ing ing 兵 bing3 21 ui ui 推 tui1 22 un un / ün 轮 询 lun2 / xun2 23 vn ün - Only used when evaluating a single final in the Pinyin question type 24 ve üe 略 lve4 25 ia ia 加 jia1 26 iao iao 表 biao3 27 ian ian 点 dian3 28 iang iang 两 liang3 29 iong iong 雄 xiong2 30 ua ua 夸 kua1 32 uai uai 怀 huai2 32 uan uan / üan 团 圆 tuan2 / yuan2 33 uang uang 矿 kuang4</description></item><item><title/><link>https://kevinkaul.github.io/mode/en-basic/chapter-result/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kevinkaul.github.io/mode/en-basic/chapter-result/</guid><description>English paragraph evaluation question type returns the original result # Final evaluation result # { &amp;#34;accuracy&amp;#34;:71.0856475830078, &amp;#34;endTime&amp;#34;:8260, &amp;#34;fluency&amp;#34;:85.3683471679688, &amp;#34;hypothesis&amp;#34;:&amp;#34;i believe there is person who brings sunshine into life person may have enough to spread around&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;integrity&amp;#34;:82.6015625, &amp;#34;overall&amp;#34;:82.368522644043, &amp;#34;refText&amp;#34;:&amp;#34;I believe there is a person who brings sunshine into your life. That person may have enough to spread around.&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;sentenceInfo&amp;#34;:[ { &amp;#34;endTime&amp;#34;:4390, &amp;#34;fluency&amp;#34;:{ &amp;#34;overall&amp;#34;:84.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://kevinkaul.github.io/mode/en-basic/phoneme-result/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kevinkaul.github.io/mode/en-basic/phoneme-result/</guid><description>English phoneme evaluation question type returns the original result # Final evaluation result # { &amp;#34;accuracy&amp;#34;: 98.1348571777344, &amp;#34;endTime&amp;#34;: 770, &amp;#34;hypothesis&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;t iy&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;integrity&amp;#34;: 100, &amp;#34;overall&amp;#34;: 98.1348571777344, &amp;#34;phonemes&amp;#34;: [ { &amp;#34;endTime&amp;#34;: 380, &amp;#34;hypothesis&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;t&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;phoneme&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;t&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;score&amp;#34;: 96.6922836303711, &amp;#34;startTime&amp;#34;: 160, &amp;#34;type&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;normal&amp;#34; }, { &amp;#34;endTime&amp;#34;: 770, &amp;#34;hypothesis&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;iy&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;phoneme&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;iy&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;score&amp;#34;: 99.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://kevinkaul.github.io/mode/en-basic/sentence-result/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kevinkaul.github.io/mode/en-basic/sentence-result/</guid><description>English sentence evaluation question type returns the original result # Final evaluation result # { &amp;#34;accuracy&amp;#34;:69.2425308227539, &amp;#34;endTime&amp;#34;:1090, &amp;#34;fluency&amp;#34;:{ &amp;#34;overall&amp;#34;:97.6374969482422, &amp;#34;pause&amp;#34;:0, &amp;#34;speed&amp;#34;:1 }, &amp;#34;hypothesis&amp;#34;:&amp;#34;hi there&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;integrity&amp;#34;:50.126871557412, &amp;#34;overall&amp;#34;:73.1748123168945, &amp;#34;refText&amp;#34;:&amp;#34;Hi there.&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;rhythm&amp;#34;:{ &amp;#34;overall&amp;#34;:0, &amp;#34;sense&amp;#34;:0, &amp;#34;stress&amp;#34;:0, &amp;#34;tone&amp;#34;:0 }, &amp;#34;startTime&amp;#34;:440, &amp;#34;waveTime&amp;#34;:1224, &amp;#34;wordInfo&amp;#34;:[ { &amp;#34;accuracy&amp;#34;:99.0998077392578, &amp;#34;endTime&amp;#34;:740, &amp;#34;fluency&amp;#34;:100, &amp;#34;hypothesis&amp;#34;:&amp;#34;hi&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;integrity&amp;#34;:100, &amp;#34;refText&amp;#34;:&amp;#34;Hi&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;rhythm&amp;#34;:{ &amp;#34;liaisonRef&amp;#34;:0, &amp;#34;liaisonScore&amp;#34;:0, &amp;#34;senseRef&amp;#34;:0, &amp;#34;senseScore&amp;#34;:0, &amp;#34;stressRef&amp;#34;:0, &amp;#34;stressScore&amp;#34;:0, &amp;#34;toneRef&amp;#34;:0, &amp;#34;toneScore&amp;#34;:0 }, &amp;#34;score&amp;#34;:99.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://kevinkaul.github.io/mode/en-basic/word-result/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kevinkaul.github.io/mode/en-basic/word-result/</guid><description>English word evaluation question type returns the original result # Final evaluation result # { &amp;#34;accuracy&amp;#34;:98.8102645874023, &amp;#34;endTime&amp;#34;:1420, &amp;#34;hypothesis&amp;#34;:&amp;#34;good morning&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;overall&amp;#34;:98.4839477539062, &amp;#34;refText&amp;#34;:&amp;#34;good morning&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;startTime&amp;#34;:340, &amp;#34;waveTime&amp;#34;:1512, &amp;#34;wordInfo&amp;#34;:[ { &amp;#34;accuracy&amp;#34;:98.0167541503906, &amp;#34;endTime&amp;#34;:640, &amp;#34;hypothesis&amp;#34;:&amp;#34;good&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;refText&amp;#34;:&amp;#34;good&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;rhythm&amp;#34;:{ &amp;#34;stressRef&amp;#34;:0, &amp;#34;stressScore&amp;#34;:0 }, &amp;#34;score&amp;#34;:98.2038116455078, &amp;#34;startTime&amp;#34;:340, &amp;#34;syllables&amp;#34;:[ { &amp;#34;endTime&amp;#34;:640, &amp;#34;phonemes&amp;#34;:[ { &amp;#34;endTime&amp;#34;:500, &amp;#34;hypothesis&amp;#34;:&amp;#34;g&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;ph2alpha&amp;#34;:&amp;#34;g&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;phid&amp;#34;:&amp;#34;1&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;phoneme&amp;#34;:&amp;#34;g&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;score&amp;#34;:94.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://kevinkaul.github.io/mode/intro_http/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kevinkaul.github.io/mode/intro_http/</guid><description>题型简介 # 点击题型名称可查看详细文档。
英文题型 # 语种代码（langType）：en-US
基础题型 # 题型名称 题型代码 音频时长限制 文件大小限制 参考文本长度限制 音标 phoneme 20 秒 1 MB 100 字符 单词 word 20 秒 1 MB 100 字符 句子 sentence 40 秒 1.5 MB 300 字符 段落 chapter 300 秒 10 MB 1 万字符 单词纠错 wordcheck 20 秒 1 MB 100 字符 句子纠错 sentencecheck 40 秒 1.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://kevinkaul.github.io/mode/zh-basic/chapter-result/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kevinkaul.github.io/mode/zh-basic/chapter-result/</guid><description>Chinese Paragraphs evaluation question type returns the original result # { &amp;#34;accuracy&amp;#34;:17.9412593841553, &amp;#34;audioInfo&amp;#34;:{ &amp;#34;clip&amp;#34;:0, &amp;#34;snr&amp;#34;:17.076961517334, &amp;#34;tipId&amp;#34;:&amp;#34;90001&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;volume&amp;#34;:48.274528503418 }, &amp;#34;endTime&amp;#34;:3880, &amp;#34;fluency&amp;#34;:57.9564590454102, &amp;#34;integrity&amp;#34;:19.7368431091309, &amp;#34;overall&amp;#34;:16.9093647003174, &amp;#34;phn&amp;#34;:17.9412593841553, &amp;#34;pinyin&amp;#34;:&amp;#34;wo3 de0 xin1 bu4 jin1 yi2 chan4 duo1 ke3 ai4 de0 xiao3 sheng1 ling2 a1 dui4 ren2 wu2 suo3 qiu2 gei3 ren2 de0 que4 shi4 ji2 hao3 de0 dong1 xi1 mi4 feng1 shi4 zai4 niang4 mi4 you4 shi4 zai4 niang4 zao4 sheng1 huo2 bu2 shi4 wei4 zi4 ji3 er2 shi4 zai4 wei2 ren2 lei4 niang4 zao4 zui4 tian2 de0 sheng1 huo2 mi4 feng1 shi4 miao2 xiao3 de0 mi4 feng1 que4 you4 duo1 me0 gao1 shang4 a1&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;refText&amp;#34;:&amp;#34;我的心不禁一颤：多可爱的小生灵啊！对人无所求，给人的却是极好的东西。蜜蜂是在酿蜜，又是在酿造生活；不是为自己，而是在为人类酿造最甜的生活。蜜蜂是渺小的；蜜蜂却又多么高尚啊！&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;rhythm&amp;#34;:{ &amp;#34;er&amp;#34;:100, &amp;#34;overall&amp;#34;:58.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://kevinkaul.github.io/mode/zh-basic/phoneme-result/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kevinkaul.github.io/mode/zh-basic/phoneme-result/</guid><description>Hanyu phoneme evaluation question type returns the original result # { &amp;#34;accuracy&amp;#34;:42.211856842041, &amp;#34;audioInfo&amp;#34;:{ &amp;#34;clip&amp;#34;:0, &amp;#34;snr&amp;#34;:56.9798812866211, &amp;#34;tipId&amp;#34;:&amp;#34;00000&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;volume&amp;#34;:50.2439613342285 }, &amp;#34;endTime&amp;#34;:9000, &amp;#34;fluency&amp;#34;:0, &amp;#34;integrity&amp;#34;:0, &amp;#34;overall&amp;#34;:0, &amp;#34;phn&amp;#34;:100, &amp;#34;refText&amp;#34;:&amp;#34;i u v b po1 mo1(*) fo&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;startTime&amp;#34;:120, &amp;#34;syllables&amp;#34;:[ { &amp;#34;endTime&amp;#34;:1640, &amp;#34;overall&amp;#34;:56.281078338623, &amp;#34;phn&amp;#34;:49.6911392211914, &amp;#34;phonemes&amp;#34;:[ { &amp;#34;endTime&amp;#34;:1640, &amp;#34;phoneme&amp;#34;:&amp;#34;i&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;score&amp;#34;:99.3822784423828, &amp;#34;startTime&amp;#34;:1600 } ], &amp;#34;refText&amp;#34;:&amp;#34;i &amp;#34;, &amp;#34;startTime&amp;#34;:120, &amp;#34;toneConfidence&amp;#34;:[ 0, 31, 17, 48, 4 ], &amp;#34;toneRef&amp;#34;:1, &amp;#34;toneScore&amp;#34;:69.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://kevinkaul.github.io/mode/zh-basic/sentence-result/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kevinkaul.github.io/mode/zh-basic/sentence-result/</guid><description>Chinese sentence evaluation question type returns the original result # { &amp;#34;accuracy&amp;#34;:92.8462142944336, &amp;#34;audioInfo&amp;#34;:{ &amp;#34;clip&amp;#34;:0, &amp;#34;snr&amp;#34;:57.8266677856445, &amp;#34;tipId&amp;#34;:&amp;#34;00000&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;volume&amp;#34;:60.88525390625 }, &amp;#34;characters&amp;#34;:[ { &amp;#34;endTime&amp;#34;:920, &amp;#34;erRef&amp;#34;:0, &amp;#34;erScore&amp;#34;:0, &amp;#34;fluency&amp;#34;:60.3578758239746, &amp;#34;overall&amp;#34;:96.5647888183594, &amp;#34;phn&amp;#34;:94.9913635253906, &amp;#34;pinyin&amp;#34;:&amp;#34;zao&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;refText&amp;#34;:&amp;#34;早&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;startTime&amp;#34;:530, &amp;#34;toneConfidence&amp;#34;:[ 0, 0, 0, 99, 1 ], &amp;#34;senseRef&amp;#34;:0, &amp;#34;senseScore&amp;#34;:0, &amp;#34;toneRef&amp;#34;:3, &amp;#34;toneScore&amp;#34;:99.9748077392578, &amp;#34;intonationRef&amp;#34;:0, &amp;#34;intonationScore&amp;#34;:0, &amp;#34;elongationRef&amp;#34;:0, &amp;#34;elongationScore&amp;#34;:0, &amp;#34;type&amp;#34;:&amp;#34;normal&amp;#34; }, { &amp;#34;endTime&amp;#34;:1320, &amp;#34;erRef&amp;#34;:0, &amp;#34;erScore&amp;#34;:0, &amp;#34;fluency&amp;#34;:96.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://kevinkaul.github.io/mode/zh-basic/word-result/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kevinkaul.github.io/mode/zh-basic/word-result/</guid><description>Chinese word evaluation question type returns the original result # { &amp;#34;phn&amp;#34;:98.4839477539062, &amp;#34;endTime&amp;#34;:830, &amp;#34;refText&amp;#34;:&amp;#34;早 早点&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;pinyin&amp;#34;:&amp;#34;zao3 zao2 dian3&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;overall&amp;#34;:95.7539062483947, &amp;#34;phn&amp;#34;:98.6248394775390, &amp;#34;toneScore&amp;#34;:96.4839470627539, &amp;#34;startTime&amp;#34;:340, &amp;#34;waveTime&amp;#34;:1020, &amp;#34;evalId&amp;#34;:&amp;#34;b1195999-1446-4a71-a671-699c2ceb607f&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;timestamp&amp;#34;:1670465928, &amp;#34;characters&amp;#34;:[ { &amp;#34;refText&amp;#34;:&amp;#34;早&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;pinyin&amp;#34;:&amp;#34;zao&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;overall&amp;#34;:95.7402381026458, &amp;#34;phn&amp;#34;:93.0264815874023, &amp;#34;toneRef&amp;#34;:3, &amp;#34;toneConfidence&amp;#34;:[ 0, 0, 0, 94, 6 ], &amp;#34;toneScore&amp;#34;:94.5887116883365, &amp;#34;type&amp;#34;:&amp;#34;normal&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;startTime&amp;#34;:128, &amp;#34;endTime&amp;#34;:260, &amp;#34;phonemes&amp;#34;:[ { &amp;#34;phoneme&amp;#34;:&amp;#34;z&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;score&amp;#34;:98.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://kevinkaul.github.io/sdk/signature_c/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kevinkaul.github.io/sdk/signature_c/</guid><description>C sample code # static void ZY_hmac_sha1(__u8 *key,__s32 key_len,__u8 *data,__s32 data_len,__u8 *digest) { __s32 b = 64; /* blocksize */ __u8 ipad = 0x36; __u8 opad = 0x5c; __u8 k0[64]; __u8 k0xorIpad[64]; __u8 step7data[64]; __u8 step5data[4096+128]; __u8 step8data[64+20]; __s32 i=0; ukit_memset(k0,0,sizeof(k0)); ukit_memset(k0xorIpad,0,sizeof(k0xorIpad)); ukit_memset(step7data,0,sizeof(step7data)); ukit_memset(step5data,0,sizeof(step5data)); ukit_memset(step8data,0,sizeof(step8data)); for (i=0; i&amp;lt;64; i++) { k0[i] = 0x00; } if (key_len !</description></item><item><title/><link>https://kevinkaul.github.io/sdk/signature_cs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kevinkaul.github.io/sdk/signature_cs/</guid><description>C# sample code # public static string HMACSHA1Text(string stringToSign,string appSecret) { HMACSHA1 hmacsha1 = new HMACSHA1(); hmacsha1.Key = System.Text.Encoding.UTF8.GetBytes(appSecret); byte[] dataBuffer = System.Text.Encoding.UTF8.GetBytes(stringToSign); byte[] hashBytes = hmacsha1.ComputeHash(dataBuffer); return Convert.ToBase64String(hashBytes); } long timestamp = (long)(DateTime.UtcNow - new DateTime(1970, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, DateTimeKind.Utc)).TotalSeconds; string stringToSign = &amp;#34;appId=&amp;#34; + appId + &amp;#34;&amp;amp;timestamp=&amp;#34; + timestamp.ToString(); string signature = HMACSHA1Text(stringToSign, appSecret)</description></item><item><title/><link>https://kevinkaul.github.io/sdk/signature_golang/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kevinkaul.github.io/sdk/signature_golang/</guid><description>Golang sample code # import ( &amp;#34;bytes&amp;#34; &amp;#34;crypto/hmac&amp;#34; &amp;#34;crypto/sha1&amp;#34; &amp;#34;encoding/base64&amp;#34; &amp;#34;time&amp;#34; ) func getSignature(appId, appSecret string) string { s := fmt.Sprintf(&amp;#34;appId=%s&amp;amp;timestamp=%d&amp;#34;, appId, time.Now().Unix()) mac := hmac.New(sha1.New, []byte(appSecret)) mac.Write([]byte(s)) return base64.StdEncoding.EncodeToString(mac.Sum(nil)) }</description></item><item><title/><link>https://kevinkaul.github.io/sdk/signature_java/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kevinkaul.github.io/sdk/signature_java/</guid><description>Java sample code # import java.util.Base64; import javax.crypto.Mac; import javax.crypto.spec.SecretKeySpec; public static String calculateRFC2104HMAC(String stringToSign, String appSecret) { SecretKeySpec signingKey = new SecretKeySpec(appSecret.getBytes(),&amp;#34;HmacSHA1&amp;#34;); Mac mac = Mac.getInstance(&amp;#34;HmacSHA1&amp;#34;); mac.init(signingKey); byte[] hashBytes = mac.doFinal(stringToSign.getBytes()); return Base64.getEncoder().encodeToString(hashBytes); } String timestamp = Long.toString(System.currentTimeMillis() / 1000); String stringToSign = &amp;#34;appId=&amp;#34; + appId + &amp;#34;&amp;amp;timestamp=&amp;#34; + timestamp; String signature = calculateRFC2104HMAC(stringToSign, appSecret)</description></item><item><title/><link>https://kevinkaul.github.io/sdk/signature_python/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kevinkaul.github.io/sdk/signature_python/</guid><description>Python sample code # import hashlib import hmac def _hmac_sha1(data, secret): return str(base64.b64encode(hmac.new(bytes(secret, &amp;#39;utf-8&amp;#39;), bytes(data, &amp;#39;utf-8&amp;#39;), hashlib.sha1).digest()), &amp;#39;utf-8&amp;#39;) timestamp = str(int(time.time())) string_to_sign = &amp;#34;appId=&amp;#34; + app_id + &amp;#34;&amp;amp;timestamp=&amp;#34; + timestamp signature = _hmac_sha1(string_to_sign, app_secret)</description></item></channel></rss>